{
  "level": "A1",
  "topic_key": "giorni_mesi",
  "topic_name": "Giorni della settimana e mesi",
  "exercises": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "dicembre",
        "domenica",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "dicembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: dicembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "sabato",
        "settembre",
        "agosto"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "settembre",
        "marzo",
        "novembre"
      ],
      "answer": "novembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: novembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "maggio",
        "sabato",
        "febbraio"
      ],
      "answer": "febbraio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: febbraio"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "giugno",
        "marzo"
      ],
      "answer": "marzo",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: marzo"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "dicembre",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "febbraio",
        "dicembre"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "marzo",
        "giugno",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giugno",
        "dicembre",
        "sabato"
      ],
      "answer": "dicembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: dicembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "luglio",
        "febbraio"
      ],
      "answer": "febbraio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: febbraio"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "dicembre",
        "aprile",
        "gennaio"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "dicembre",
        "lunedì",
        "gennaio"
      ],
      "answer": "gennaio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: gennaio"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "settembre",
        "febbraio",
        "mercoledì"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "venerdì",
        "maggio"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "mercoledì",
        "giugno",
        "settembre"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "marzo",
        "ottobre",
        "agosto"
      ],
      "answer": "ottobre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: ottobre"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "agosto",
        "mercoledì",
        "martedì"
      ],
      "answer": "mercoledì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: mercoledì"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "novembre",
        "domenica",
        "marzo"
      ],
      "answer": "novembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: novembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "gennaio",
        "sabato",
        "martedì"
      ],
      "answer": "sabato",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: sabato"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "settembre",
        "maggio",
        "ottobre"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "maggio",
        "agosto",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "maggio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: maggio"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "gennaio",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "lunedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: lunedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "domenica",
        "sabato"
      ],
      "answer": "lunedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: lunedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "settembre",
        "sabato",
        "novembre"
      ],
      "answer": "sabato",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: sabato"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "novembre",
        "gennaio",
        "ottobre"
      ],
      "answer": "novembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: novembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "aprile",
        "martedì",
        "ottobre"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "mercoledì",
        "settembre"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "febbraio",
        "luglio",
        "martedì"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "luglio",
        "settembre"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "giugno",
        "sabato"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "maggio",
        "febbraio"
      ],
      "answer": "febbraio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: febbraio"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "maggio",
        "febbraio",
        "settembre"
      ],
      "answer": "febbraio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: febbraio"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "mercoledì",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "lunedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: lunedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "aprile",
        "dicembre",
        "agosto"
      ],
      "answer": "dicembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: dicembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "marzo",
        "domenica",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "marzo",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: marzo"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "gennaio",
        "lunedì",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "dicembre",
        "venerdì",
        "luglio"
      ],
      "answer": "venerdì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: venerdì"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "mercoledì",
        "luglio",
        "settembre"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giugno",
        "giovedì",
        "dicembre"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "aprile",
        "giovedì",
        "agosto"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giugno",
        "giovedì",
        "domenica"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giugno",
        "domenica",
        "agosto"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "mercoledì",
        "lunedì",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "sabato",
        "giugno",
        "lunedì"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "maggio",
        "venerdì"
      ],
      "answer": "maggio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: maggio"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "dicembre",
        "giugno",
        "maggio"
      ],
      "answer": "maggio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: maggio"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "gennaio",
        "sabato",
        "mercoledì"
      ],
      "answer": "sabato",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: sabato"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "venerdì",
        "martedì"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "sabato",
        "venerdì",
        "lunedì"
      ],
      "answer": "lunedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: lunedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "martedì",
        "giovedì",
        "novembre"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "martedì",
        "sabato",
        "mercoledì"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "agosto",
        "sabato",
        "martedì"
      ],
      "answer": "agosto",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: agosto"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giugno",
        "luglio",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "luglio",
        "venerdì",
        "lunedì"
      ],
      "answer": "luglio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: luglio"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "gennaio",
        "novembre",
        "giugno"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "mercoledì",
        "febbraio"
      ],
      "answer": "mercoledì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: mercoledì"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "luglio",
        "novembre",
        "martedì"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "martedì",
        "maggio",
        "sabato"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "dicembre",
        "giugno"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "luglio",
        "lunedì",
        "dicembre"
      ],
      "answer": "luglio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: luglio"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "luglio",
        "maggio",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "maggio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: maggio"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "settembre",
        "dicembre",
        "giugno"
      ],
      "answer": "dicembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: dicembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "sabato",
        "lunedì",
        "dicembre"
      ],
      "answer": "sabato",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: sabato"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "maggio",
        "ottobre",
        "giugno"
      ],
      "answer": "maggio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: maggio"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "sabato",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "sabato",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: sabato"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "martedì",
        "mercoledì"
      ],
      "answer": "giovedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giovedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "settembre",
        "giugno"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "mercoledì",
        "maggio",
        "lunedì"
      ],
      "answer": "lunedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: lunedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "gennaio",
        "febbraio",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "febbraio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: febbraio"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "dicembre",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "dicembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: dicembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "febbraio",
        "giovedì",
        "maggio"
      ],
      "answer": "giovedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giovedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "gennaio",
        "lunedì",
        "ottobre"
      ],
      "answer": "lunedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: lunedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "giugno",
        "giovedì"
      ],
      "answer": "lunedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: lunedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "marzo",
        "luglio"
      ],
      "answer": "luglio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: luglio"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "gennaio",
        "settembre",
        "novembre"
      ],
      "answer": "novembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: novembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "settembre",
        "giugno",
        "agosto"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "ottobre",
        "novembre"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "aprile",
        "luglio"
      ],
      "answer": "giovedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giovedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "venerdì",
        "sabato",
        "marzo"
      ],
      "answer": "marzo",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: marzo"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "aprile",
        "novembre",
        "venerdì"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "febbraio",
        "maggio",
        "martedì"
      ],
      "answer": "maggio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: maggio"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giugno",
        "sabato",
        "lunedì"
      ],
      "answer": "giugno",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giugno"
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "febbraio",
        "martedì",
        "lunedì"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "giovedì",
        "novembre",
        "lunedì"
      ],
      "answer": "giovedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: giovedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "marzo",
        "aprile",
        "novembre"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "novembre",
        "agosto"
      ],
      "answer": "novembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: novembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "venerdì",
        "domenica",
        "giugno"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "martedì",
        "ottobre"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "settembre",
        "lunedì",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "settembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: settembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "martedì",
        "agosto",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "agosto",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: agosto"
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "sabato",
        "venerdì",
        "dicembre"
      ],
      "answer": "dicembre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: dicembre"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "luglio",
        "domenica",
        "gennaio"
      ],
      "answer": "luglio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: luglio"
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "aprile",
        "luglio"
      ],
      "answer": "luglio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: luglio"
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "martedì",
        "lunedì",
        "maggio"
      ],
      "answer": "maggio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: maggio"
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "martedì",
        "maggio",
        "ottobre"
      ],
      "answer": "ottobre",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: ottobre"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "martedì",
        "febbraio",
        "marzo"
      ],
      "answer": "martedì",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: martedì"
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "lunedì",
        "ottobre",
        "aprile"
      ],
      "answer": "aprile",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: aprile"
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "domenica",
        "maggio",
        "sabato"
      ],
      "answer": "domenica",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: domenica"
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "marzo",
        "novembre",
        "luglio"
      ],
      "answer": "marzo",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: marzo"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "novembre",
        "gennaio",
        "domenica"
      ],
      "answer": "gennaio",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: gennaio"
    }
  ]
}